{"question": "What was the biggest counter-terrorism operation in Australia's history?", "answer": "A"}
{"question": "Who were the contestants?", "answer": "Miss"}
{"question": "Who was responsible for the ambush?", "answer": "The"}
{"question": "What caused the Brisbane hailstorm in 2014?", "answer": "The"}
{"question": "What is the Article 132 of the Costa Rican Constitution that outlines the procedures for the election of the president?", "answer": "The"}
{"question": "What is the 2014 World Team Table Tennis Championships?", "answer": "It"}
{"question": "What was the name of the British Academy of Film and Television Arts (BAFTA) award ceremony where Stephen Mangan presided over the event?", "answer": "The"}
{"question": "Who is the investigative judge leading the Operation Car Wash investigation?", "answer": "Sérgio"}
{"question": "What is the majority system used for the elections in full by the majority system?", "answer": "The"}
{"question": "What was the name of the 82-year-old woman whose back garden in Edmonton was beheaded by 25-year-old Nicholas Salvador?", "answer": "Palmira"}
{"question": "What caused the Annot derailment?", "answer": "A"}
{"question": "How old was Breck David Lafave Bednar when he was murdered by Lewis Daynes in February 2014?", "answer": "Breck"}
{"question": "What is the moment magnitude of the 2014 Vrancea earthquake?", "answer": "5.7"}
{"question": "What was the impact of Typhoon Hagupit on the Philippines in 2014?", "answer": "Hagupit"}
{"question": "How did the project begin?", "answer": "David"}
{"question": "Who won the South Yorkshire Police and Crime Commissioner by-election?", "answer": "Mark"}
{"question": "Who died in the Heywood and Middleton by-election?", "answer": "Jim"}
{"question": "Which opposition party won the elections in Antigua and Barbuda?", "answer": "Antigua"}
{"question": "What is its size compared to other tumuli in Greece?", "answer": "Dwarfs"}
{"question": "What species is known from at least six young adult individuals?", "answer": "Patagotitan"}
{"question": "What is the name of the marathon race in Tokyo, Japan, which was held on February 23, 2014?", "answer": "Tokyo"}
{"question": "What were the causes of the 2014 unrest in Bosnia and Herzegovina?", "answer": "The"}
{"question": "What is the Local Audit and Accountability Act 2014?", "answer": "The"}
{"question": "What were the reported casualties in the clashes?", "answer": "Some"}
{"question": "What is the Dangam district of Kunar?", "answer": "The"}
{"question": "What is the name of the professional wrestling event series that NJPW and CMLL co-produced?", "answer": "Fantastica"}
{"question": "What was Cyclone Christina's landfall?", "answer": "The"}
{"question": "What was the name of the co-host city for the 2015 World Junior Ice Hockey Championships?", "answer": "Toronto"}
{"question": "Can you summarize the given passage about an Asian woman who was found dead near a trail in Yellowknife, Canada?", "answer": "Around"}
{"question": "Who won Miss France 2015?", "answer": "Miss"}
{"question": "How many people were on board the MV Miraj-4 at the time of the accident?", "answer": "Between"}
{"question": "Which party/candidate is Kim Kielsen leading a coalition with in the First Cabinet of Kim Kielsen?", "answer": "Forward"}
{"question": "How powerful was the March 2014 nor'easter?", "answer": "Extratropical"}
{"question": "Which film won the Best Film award at the 28th Goya Awards?", "answer": "The"}
{"question": "What is the name of the mosque located in Plovdiv, Bulgaria?", "answer": "Dzhumaya"}
{"question": "What is the head of state's name?", "answer": "Juan"}
{"question": "What weapons were used in the parade, and how many were present?", "answer": "The"}
{"question": "What is Galatasaray's aim for an unprecedented twenty league titles?", "answer": "Galatasaray"}
{"question": "What is the name of the 2013–14 Coupe de France Final?", "answer": "The"}
{"question": "How much of the debt is to be resumed by Argentina?", "answer": "76"}
{"question": "What was the name of the July Crisis?", "answer": "The"}
{"question": "What is the name of the Socialist Party mayoral candidate elected in the 2014 Paris Municipal elections?", "answer": "Anne"}
{"question": "What is the moment magnitude of the 2014 Mexico–Guatemala earthquake?", "answer": "6.9"}
{"question": "How long is the 2014 European Aquatics Championships in Berlin?", "answer": "The"}
{"question": "How did the photograph of Ed Miliband eating a bacon sandwich become a source of sustained commentary and the subject of an internet meme in 2014 and 2015?", "answer": "A"}
{"question": "What is the second sentence of the passage?", "answer": "The"}
{"question": "What was the name of the residency by Kate Bush at the Hammersmith Apollo in 2014?", "answer": "Before"}
{"question": "How did Sharon die and what were the international responses to his death?", "answer": "Sharon"}
{"question": "What is the Canada-Korea Free Trade Agreement?", "answer": "The"}
{"question": "How many candidates ran for each seat?", "answer": "There"}
{"question": "Which international agreements were part of the Minsk agreements?", "answer": "The"}
{"question": "What is the name of the professional wrestling event promoted by DDT Pro-Wrestling that featured Ryōgoku Peter Pan 2014?:?", "answer": "Ryōgoku"}
{"question": "What is the legal case involving two HIV-positive non-citizen prisoners seeking access to antiretroviral (ARV) medication at state expense?", "answer": "Tapela"}
{"question": "What issues was the domestic stability referred to in the passage?", "answer": "Domestic"}
{"question": "How long did the excavation take?", "answer": "The"}
{"question": "Which children and one adult died in the fire?", "answer": "According"}
{"question": "What was the internal conflict in the Central African Republic that started essentially on 13 April 2013, and who were the parties involved?", "answer": "The"}
{"question": "What is Operation Okra, and what is its purpose?", "answer": "Operation"}
{"question": "Who was the reigning Miss Brazil at the time of the pageant, and who was crowned her successor?", "answer": "Jakelyne"}
{"question": "Who won the 2014 Tokyo gubernatorial election?", "answer": "Yōichi"}
{"question": "What are the details of the 2013–14 Burkinabé Premier League?", "answer": "The"}
{"question": "Which ammunition depots were the two explosions in Vlachovice?", "answer": "The"}
{"question": "Can you summarize the Economic Adjustment Programme for Cyprus?", "answer": "The"}
{"question": "What is the name of the 2014 FIBA World Championship for Women, and where did it take place?", "answer": "The"}
{"question": "What are the two suspects suspected of in the case?", "answer": "Rv"}
{"question": "What is the location of the Union Glacier Station?", "answer": "The"}
{"question": "What was the Chinese Golf Factory Workers Strike for Essential Rights, and why did it occur in Shenzhen?", "answer": "The"}
{"question": "What is the EBU, and what is the Eurovision Debate?", "answer": "The"}
{"question": "Which member states addressed the General Debate of the sixty-ninth session of the United Nations General Assembly?", "answer": "Leaders"}
{"question": "What fields are discussed in the conferences and workshops in the Vienna Summer of Logic?", "answer": "The"}
{"question": "How long was the Hampden Bridge?", "answer": "It"}
{"question": "What caused the crackdown in Satkhira district?", "answer": "The"}
{"question": "What was the target of the suicide bomber at the Taverna du Liban?", "answer": "The"}
{"question": "How many points did Azerbaijan score in the final of Eurovision 2014?", "answer": "11th"}
{"question": "What was the destination of MH370?", "answer": "Malaysia"}
{"question": "Where did the missing man, Lars Joachim Mittank, go missing?", "answer": "Varna"}
{"question": "What was the largest outbreak of Zika fever in Oceania?", "answer": "It"}
{"question": "Who is the current Miss Colombia?", "answer": "Paulina"}
{"question": "How many people died in the accident?", "answer": "The"}
{"question": "Who won the BAFTA Award for Best Supporting Actor?", "answer": "Christopher"}
{"question": "How many people were killed in the mudslides in Argo District, Badakhshan Province, Afghanistan?", "answer": "350"}
{"question": "What is the purpose of the Exempted Limited Partnership Law, 2014 (Law 5 of 2014)?", "answer": "It"}
{"question": "What is the joint declaration made by Cyprus and Turkey on 11 February 2014, and what is its significance?", "answer": "The"}
{"question": "What is the author's view on the lack of water in Caleta Olivia?", "answer": "The"}
{"question": "What caused the flash floods in northeastern Bulgaria on June 19, 2014?", "answer": "Torrential"}
{"question": "What is gutter oil and trench oil?", "answer": "Gutter"}
{"question": "How did the journalists respond to their detention?", "answer": "The"}
{"question": "Which councils were elected in the local elections in Georgia?", "answer": "The"}
{"question": "What was the attack on the Indian consulate in Herat, Afghanistan?", "answer": "Four"}
{"question": "What was the purpose of the emergency meeting?", "answer": "To"}
{"question": "What was the theme of the South Asian Association of Regional Cooperation (SAARC) summit held in Kathmandu in November 2014?", "answer": "Promoting"}
{"question": "Who is the songwriter of the song \"Greece 2014\" by Sophia Patsalides?", "answer": "The"}
{"question": "What was the Best Actor award given for in the 31st Robert Awards?", "answer": "Daniel"}
{"question": "What was the heatwave in Spain leading to the heavy storms in Europe?", "answer": "A"}
{"question": "How did the earthquake occur?", "answer": "An"}
{"question": "What did Canadian Prime Minister Stephen Harper announce on 3 October 2014?", "answer": "A"}
{"question": "Can you summarize the incident described in the passage about the Thai woman Pattaramon Janbua who sought to raise money for an Australian couple?", "answer": "An"}
{"question": "What is the date of the General Elections in Bolivia?", "answer": "October"}
{"question": "Who attended the summit?", "answer": "The"}
{"question": "What is the name of Hamas' military tunnel network?", "answer": "The"}
